so we'll have to push I guess I could
just push from github bathtub okay cool
so here on my Windows computer we're
gonna wait for some people to show up
today is chill stream it's chill
oh that's exciting that it's your
birthday but I do have to say that these
dreams are all about me
these dreams exists to glorify my ego
not I don't know man it's early happy
birthday my 3xx you are the first person
to speak wait are you a subscriber does
that mean all your trich prime ok that's
almost to subscribe where we love our
subscribers because they give me money
and I spend money on great thing it's
like tea here we are we're drinking or
drinking tea you know what was I
thinking this morning
somebody in a comment
call me melodramatic melodramatic I
looked it up
especially in being exaggerated
sensationalized or overly emotional oh
no man
it wins 5 out of 12 games bro you're
almost halfway there you know it's like
you have a self-driving car they can
drive on 5 out of every 12 streets
you're almost halfway there yeah yeah
yeah so Windows the most common
operating system in the world we're also
trying out vs code today and I really
used to before
so let's first get checked out - be
Cash's now we have a branch let's run
the mini p-value tests so for those of
you who don't know many TV displays
distributed file system it's now used at
comma
you have to allow access through the
fire that's our test oh yeah that's just
for rebuilding and stuff so first thing
that we're gonna have to do is look at
these two record and from record things
you all just stick the hash on the
suffix this has suffix not valid oh my
god you all think I'm on drugs you know
what greedy
you know what greedy BAM that's right
it's ban you arey is bad morning what
that sound is is my laundry we're doing
laundry okay is there been keybindings 4
vs code how do I get vim keybindings
we're gonna waste the whole stream doing
crap like that boom keybindings
yes color this probably has one of these
stupid plug-in architectures
[Music]
your subscriber you get away with more I
just look at somebody and I don't see a
star next to their name and I don't see
a crown next to their name then I'm like
get the fuck out of my channel anyway so
hard to use alright guys I'm sorry to do
this to you but we got to go put the
clothes in the dryer so I'll be right
back
all right Pisan we're not dry clothes
it's gonna be a good deck
so many key values my distributed file
system you'll find it on my github /g oh
hi
just tell you how to install the s code
event script is not supported oh this
looks hard it's automatically enabled
install okay yeah sure yeah
press the gear in the bottom left I mean
this is what everybody is using I should
kind of learn how to deal with our 300 M
key bindings oh this is really nice this
works
[Music]
cool thanks bro
yes we're just gonna do it has suffix SS
type shit that be it's gonna be an md5 -
I got some tests for that - yes
okay you probably want to keep them as X
as well no she'll just be a string
hey how come I've in is gone we want
really what the hash to be in there and
optional
now I should really use some real
serialization thing that isn't these
stupid hacks just stop working job
I run that test 101 lip test go go test
Oh index must be non-negative ah that's
too bad too few values instruct
initializer is there a way to make
something optional and a go struct
optional this looks awful
go strong default value
I have least do that
right a seperate constructor function oh
my god
why can't I just do this why doesn't
that just work no it's gonna complain no
that's of course not gonna work because
that would make sense and you know let's
make sure my pull request make you high
you're a little boy star who's talking
about fucking calm a guy who's talking
about self-driving cars
monka monka has five ones he's booking
us fine a subscriber your subscriber you
get a warning if you're not a subscriber
to get banned no that's a layabout
market go
okay well now you don't watch you just
double prefixes yeah it works
it's office
[Music]
mismatched type string and array string
oh that's not right and now we have too
few values and structure visualizer okay
now we're just left with too few values
instructive but it's because I'm
creating records and I don't give them a
hash let's just talk about it who's
talking about it wait honestly who's
talking about you know time out time out
not the place whose monka s5o your codes
darvid you know what time out there we
go y'all gonna be nice
well you'll just risk it you know what
you you are actually bad no don't mod
user we're gonna ban music yeah there we
go
this is always you know this is really
common at the beginning of my streams or
you guys think you can get away with
shit and then you'll realize that I read
you guys know what the number one rated
a management book on Amazon s oh this is
the Dover thrift Edition here we go look
at this I got it today it's the number
one bestseller in office management you
know oh the audio is bad well I'm sorry
you can buy me a better microphone this
better that's right
oh it's not bad at all what are you all
causing trouble for all right I mean we
could just edit every place where we
create records
here right don't have a hash
perfect
now I have to go through and figure out
everywhere I created a record here we
gotta create the default record here see
that
rebalanced server creates some records
we're actually gonna want to compute the
hash here though so well we'll get to
that later first let's just add support
so the idea is we want every file to be
able to have a hash value we want to
keep it backward compatible with the
existing mini key value just and rebuild
so what rebuild does is if your database
breaks you can regenerate it okay don't
fail print Ln list and the redundant
newline what that's kind of by design or
whatever
I know so yeah maybe maybe we'll change
the name we're adding a file hashing
support but this is a Content hash it's
based around yeah it's based around
level DB which of course is already a
hash function Sergio thanks for the bits
[Music]
okay we really should have done some
test-driven development here would have
been a great example but let's get like
md5 hello
I hope those are working you can add a
println just
I kind of like that in the tests anyway
shows that they're past okay and support
to record Oh guys you know what I got
and we can go open it on the stream
I got an Apple watch I bought a series
five Apple watch yesterday and I will
push it from here we can just publish
branch perfect alright now if we go over
to github we should see my hashes branch
we can even create a pull request oh wow
this is really nice but not mob no of
course you can't do that from get a
desktop you have to do that from this is
mini key value and you'll see there's a
hashes branch how am i editing the code
directly from the server no it's not
mounted so this is just using uh it's
actually on checked out in the Windows
system you can check my commits all
right so we're gonna see kind of what
I've written so far so we added hash to
record type I added a mechanism for
parsing the hash if there's a hash
prefix I added a few more tests I
shouldn't have removed that I got
scammed but it's fine
okay we're also going to refactor
rebalance at some point to not do it
like it's doing it there isn't rebalance
call this server now right yeah those
are the ones calling the server now
whatever that code what's he's done yeah
you could separate them by something but
yeah it's a fixed length right like it's
all gonna be md5 so that's fine they're
guaranteed to have it you only need to
set null if you have non fixed length
sure might be better for the future a
lot of things might be better for the
future wait some more
[Music]
so the person who suggested hacking NASA
had it storming area 51 go that went
well
we'll consider it okay so what we're
going to need to add here
[Music]
that hash so I use hashes and live see
how I do it
yeah another sex really do five have to
import crypto md5 here yes I do
we love md5 md5 is the best hash
function ever sha-1 used to be better
but now it has collisions - who cares
it's all the same md5 dots some body
md5
TxDOT encode to string
does that work
Exploud cartridge king seems nicer
[Music]
the hatch of the value its key value
lies on file
yeah it's not doing yourself - I think
it's just WSL and if you tell me a way
to check out that many key values yeah
go a while ago the Python one was too
slow so now like let me just make sure
that my delete is not stupid
mmm I say oh it's stupid yeah it's
stupid we want to say rekt on hash here
that will persist the hash okay do the
test don't pass let's say cannot use
body type io read R by E what I've
literally copy and pasted that code all
they're doing it like that that's not
right
because what if they're zeros
the sources bite
I don't even know
okay fine you know what I'm done with
this fat guys have this worked does this
work it does have a fixed length so
maybe it is okay
multiple valued format print F in single
valued context why I want to ask printer
for something oh my god
she's legacy is disgusting alright well
that's a different problem not use md5
sum I oh we've got a new way to do this
we'll put a new hatch interface to write
to IO copy okay fine fine fine fine fine
oh that's cute never mind I do like that
better
even though does hex encoded string is
this uppercase hex or lowercase hex
okay Xperia Clark a sex is way more
beautiful
I copy ash body
[Music]
how can that error
ban the annular god wasn't the angular
got what's wrong with the angular got
what does he do to me just cruise
through her van happy doesn't mean we're
gonna bit out okay all the tests will
pass it's good
let's did I write something that after
the test run we like dump dump for that
it's kind of level d compared try our
test our test should actually fail no
Noah values mash because they have
hashes look at that
see so this key now has this hash in
front of it okay all right what it's not
she's not you want a bigger
I don't think ctrl+ work sorry
ctrl+ won't work yeah
add the hashes to here
okay now if we have a hash I think what
I want to do is just return a header W
dot header set and read the REC - is not
equal to CR out there some standard for
that so I can just make up something
again just trying to be is this editor
trying to be smart and like put braces
and for me I hate whenever there's do
that content 5i here we go I got it
right
oh it's base64-encoded for a 128-bit mv4
digest
I guess 128-bit is exactly what I'm what
I'm doing
let's read the RFC
good
content md5 generation blah blah blah
did it say it have to be base64 ah has
to be base64 cars can't help you there
that shitty you know I don't really like
that does anything I actually support
this thing
Oh was removed because it was any
consistently implemented with respect to
partial responses oh that's an
interesting problem we have that same
problem we should add a note note that
the hash is always the whole okay is
legion high of causing trouble what I
was ridiculous okay so now if I run mini
key value it's really very easy to use
um you can just curl which puts big swag
and we have now you can get key oh here
we go content md5 let's go online to
make sure that's actually the md5 a big
splat Wow
wait this is gonna be the fastest we
ever like did anything normally I say
like it's not right not nice -
that's about that huh
it's not right
should we had a print
the whole body of that request should
just be big swag what now it yes well it
says this is the md5 what is that the
md5 of
zip archive data Oh it's an empty hash
ah okay my md5 er didn't work
if we've already read the contents into
the tea reader oh yeah I messed this up
um this isn't right this is stupid arrow
stupid stuff I can just say md5sum bar
dot writes look at all those lines no
saving cannot use buff dog bites type
funk bites
ah the function then we should call it
anyway slice of on addressable value and
now we're back to this stupid problem
again so we're back to doing this
programming you don't need that anymore
pretty much back to what we had the
problem is that I was consuming the
reader and actually need a reader there
I don't know why I wrote all that code
still the wrong hash
it didn't really put okay what's the
correct ID right now
I guess the put was down leaving the
floor what happens if I try to again to
put yeah okay so yeah that's for three
okay that's fine
cool fix hash computation and return
it's not PowerShell so I setup Ubuntu
using Windows or Linux subsystem and
then I just SSH into it okay that's done
let's just try to come to test that
[Music]
again we probably could have done this
with test-driven development I don't
know we're probably gonna wash I was
gonna open that in them I'm trying not
to use them today trying to use vsco
here we go oh yes let's install the
Python extension oh it said
multi-threaded debugger that's more than
I could say from Python
[Music]
I don't even know what this does is
gonna send my code to Microsoft isn't it
sure why not it's open-source reload the
one I regret this markdown went
we use many key values distributed file
system for anything so that's our dock
content let's print the headers yes so
the problem is that isn't with a header
[Music]
I don't understand why the D became
lowercase and that just weirds me out
because I quote md5 here
but I guess that's the standard for
that's the only thing I want to check
I'm a little bit concerned about that
that printf thing
is that I mean that syntax isn't really
like sensible and server
my concern here is what if there's zeros
actually
let's just try something that has an md5
hash with a lot of zeros we're gonna
watch let's make the test better it
should be easy to compute an OD v in
Python all right let's just say data
actually ski
[Music]
come to be five what else you do import
md5 or use hash Libya exactly I know
hash lived on employed ashlynn this is
laggy er than them
wait I was already using Ashland Oh
didn't need to do that
[Music]
tax digest oh yeah love that love that
until I complete whatever shit alright
cool
okay I mean if the test passes arts has
not fails which is interesting just make
sure some of these hashes start with
zeros
about crash I see what happened
that kills us
- zero can we see one of those 0 r is
equal to zero it's just fine yeah here
we go
yeah so it must you know what we can
also yeah yeah windows firewalls upset
with me I know yeah we shouldn't of our
code crap like that and tests oh I'm
just so it's just so conditioned muscle
memory all right for some reason twitch
is telling me I have zero viewers which
I know is not true Wow three hundred
seven hundred fifty seven thank you
thank you for joining me today on this
beautiful journey where we add
functionality the mini key value little
extensions all I can search extensions
in the marketplace all I can make micro
payments to improve my editor Oh
somebody's okay yeah that all sounds
good cool okay
now I think if we go to github I think
we're gonna find out that the tests are
failing I wanted to be done but we're
not done because the tests are actually
gonna be failing I believe oh we don't
know that until we create a pull request
and create a pull request I'm not logged
in together you don't like my new sub
system I'm sorry
let me just log into my other laptop get
my to obey and screaming
I don't think they do it we just took
the rebound test the rebuild tossed
chaos and the reason the rebuild test
fails I mean in a way we could just fix
this with a hack and that problem
actually the best way to fix this
probably is just by fixing the test if
v1 is not equal to if add some
[Music]
now
so the problem is we do this test where
you rebuild the database and then
confirm that it matches but undefined
strings okay but the problem is the
rebuild doesn't recompute the hashes if
we're rebuilding just the level DB it's
optional to have the hash
good pass fix rebuild it says fail test
Valley just like I thought
yeah we you want to pay me a couple
hundred dollars right look I'll tolerate
you because you're a subscriber when I
talk about how on this channel I'm
desperate for money and I love money I'm
joking around I have more money than I
possibly know what to do with so a few
hundred dollars is not going to entice
me to do shit
now if you post it it says you are a
subscriber if you post it in the
comments we can all talk about it and if
it's good we'll be like Dan that's a
good idea and if it's stupid we'll make
funny because like Max Reed once said
bring back bullying do I talk like such
a douche IRL yes I do and your time down
woo
you want to talk by I mean you know the
trolls got me thinking do I talk like
this in a real body I mean the part of
that I'm focused on is the real life
part Odin XVI thank you for subscribing
to my channel are you trying to tell me
that my stream is not real life how do I
address patents I address them as your
majesty your majesty
great 5:33 lidar patent of the way Moe
uber lawsuit yo if you guys want to read
something sick it's New Republic it's
about the 737 max yeah this is brutal
it's brutal I love the picture you guys
know this is something I've been
following you really upsets me
finally uses Python yeah
tell us more about it come on come on
Shane Shami all right guys we already
did what we have planned to do for the
the stream today so let's go in hack a
rank do our slut hacker rank installs
and let's try to use esoteric
programming languages to solve problems
I thought this might be fun no George
what was my name do hot crap maybe
that's what I used as a password do that
what was my name from the last stream of
Geo hot junk oh good thinking yeah yeah
G hot junk you were bro what passport
did I use I don't know
forgot your password geo hot junk
probably's geo hot junket malonate or
something
oh great select pictures of bus mail
inator calm feel hot junk Oh perfect
anyone else tries to reset my password
using mail Nader I'm coming for you
all right perfect
am i open - yes I won't put to new job
opportunities absolutely my name is geo
ha junk
I live in Alaska my profile headline I'm
just I'm just I'm just upset by this I'm
just no no no Alaska
I live in Alaska okay what language
should we use you know what you know
what
all Bros Bros do you know about morgues
I think I'm what was
oh yeah using only one color see this
guy this guy is my YouTube idol one day
looking this guy's does many mores one
guy I wanna it's just laggy but if you
guys you guys should watch Morris all
right we'll use Haskell
what this looks hard
what
oh no lost no never my own play hat I
don't wanna play this anymore
we already did what today's we already
did what today's uh no it's lagging
because my monitor is 5k and I don't
actually really understand now we
already did what today's stream was what
is leak code wait where let's make sure
the tests actually passed yeah we think
the test is good
yo yo real talk don't we jail broke a
shower you ever wonder why you shower is
low-flow well you know get a pair of
pliers and a pair of needlenose pliers
and a cloth and some plumber's tape and
you can jailbreak your shower to kids
our knowns as dreamed up to all time I
don't tell you you know it's better the
environment the climate crisis division
is coming for me whoever walks up
Oh
yeah Bros is an Apple watch series 5 all
right we'll do the unboxing and then I
have a copy of Machiavelli's The Prince
to read to learn how to be a better
manager
[Music]
we needed to improve the acoustics of
the room I didn't want you to hear the
dryer
[Music]
there's a tiny
I think maybe
the information down apple.com / support
/ manuals / watch
we have three pieces I don't understand
why instead oh I guess it's how big your
wrists us this is very small residence
this is for human heart wrists
here's my Apple watch
do I have a wrist or do i have a small
wrist
how do I know which one goes home I just
hide its our picture somewhere
like
this one
perhaps I do have a small wrist
let's try this one
whoa who's using bad words in my discord
you might have my twitch okay
I need oh I could get popped up can i
pair my phone with my watch
okay I don't know about monka s I don't
know but the ASMR portion is over we
really really put stuff everywhere oh
here we go
comes with this too you can charge it I
guess
well I like these new cars Wood snaps
they're kind of beautifully designed
it's gotta be someone's job at Apple
what a guy alright open your band box
follow the steps to get started open
your Apple watch app on your Apple phone
I needed an Apple phone why didn't they
tell me
put your Apple watch and hold it up to
the camera
my iPhone is out of date sorry you can't
use the Apple watch until you download
iOS 13 no that's gonna take forever
no that's gonna take forever no my
dreams all my dreams iPhone update
stream it's downloading iOS 13 ooh
dark mode
seems vaguely Pleasant what am I gonna
do with this extra piece it upsets me
and I used to work really hard like I
would save all the all the packaging but
now I've become an adult sorry teacher
took so little time to write this is
junk this is junk what if my wrist grows
and I become fat
well then I'll you know be so upset with
myself that I'll need a pickup and buy
new Apple watch anyway because despite
what Buddhism tells you buying things
really does make you happy that's a lie
but it's a nice lie to believe because
you don't like buying things that's what
there is to do today there you can buy
things and you can post about you things
all right you can sell things but yeah
it's becoming increasingly hard
yeah hacking things is becoming harder -
they're really clamping down they're
clamping down on their control of the
internet they're clamping down on their
control of the world you are a consumer
no that's not true I lied about being
rich that was just that was just to make
fun of that guy who wanted me to do like
bro bro could you hacked my Instagram do
you hack my friend's Instagram for $27
that was mostly just that I'm really not
rich I really count on all of my
subscribers and all of you giving me
money or else I won't be able to afford
Apple watches for the next unboxings
chief
I put the dryer
I think that might be in forestry and
today Oh do universal Geneva thank you
for gifting subs to people we appreciate
you Dork moe thank you for the bits we
appreciate you
yes a smart driver that's right a lot of
smart drives oh no I can't set up the
Apple watch because iOS 13 isn't
installed yet it's still preparing
update now I want delete code it's not
that fun let's say all right let's see
let's see I don't know I've never done
lead code maybe it's super entertaining
is it super entertaining create account
is it gonna ask me dumb questions using
it yo hot jump password Geo ha Oh Geo ha
and then I'm not gonna tell you guys
what comes next cuz it's a secret oh
it's George chunk I spelled it wrong
now I can't do that anymore yeah do that
okay
median of two sorted arrays who said I
can't do the hard ones fine
the median
of the two sorted or oh wow this is all
this is verify my email all right you
know what they just made it too hard for
me you know what's it called quick
select the algorithm unordered list
on median of the two sorted arrays
it's better not interfere with my
oh you can't see anything oh I'm sorry
oh you have to look at my face us funny
no no no we definitely don't do any
portables all right median of two
sorters is it confirmed my email let's
go come on come on
gigabit internet this doesn't work I'm
gonna charge my Apple watch what we
okay the median of the two sorted arrays
I mean see this is the problem all right
well we've all we won't Google we'll
just try to think about damn look at
those uh those type signatures on that
Python um well okay so what's the
algorithm guys like this one is hard I
want to point out and it is way easier
than that one I did on well let's talk
about let's watch it talk more after I
solve it okay
med one equals
yeah you understand it has to be oh so
it's like you got to do something like
okay you got the two medians right and
you gotta like get them to converge or
some shit like right so the algorithms
probably something
this is stupid guys yeah merge the
arrays and resort well so first off you
don't have to merge the Iranian resource
it's very easy to zip the two together
but that of course would be O of M plus
N and then that's too much oh we need
less oh well it's like you guys do like
binary search on the on the things right
like you got like the the the the two
and then you're gonna move one of them
this way and you're gonna move one of
them that way right
so in an extreme case the first list
contains everybody in one case the two
lists are exactly absolutely identical
and then you want to know in an extreme
case the first list is all smaller and
the second list is all larger so you
actually want the the average of the two
now you guys do like binary search on
this
and let's say so the medium can be an
average of two but it can never be an
average of more than two so I think the
answer is gonna be yeah you're gonna
have like low and high right but do I
have to Lowe's and two highs and then I
guess I do check the last one in the
first or i of the yeah I understand
feeling like Google interview this is
hard no one knows this algorithm it's
binary search right you could search for
a single element now search for the
median right yeah well at least this is
clever at least like this isn't going to
involve a lot of code once you figure
out this solution
just merge sort and find the median yeah
that sounds great except for this oh
yeah oh yeah yeah try that try that and
see if that's you know yeah right
it doesn't that sound fun yeah here we
go
done
about syntax
well see look beautiful Wow works so
well guys oh yeah yeah there you go
all right yeah who cares this hello
again it doesn't matter nothing tea on
my shirt okay
but think about a normal medium
lisam it's not right let me handle this
case it's interesting to also note that
there's always gonna be an even number
so that's okay the different sizes so
never mind no pan thank you for
subscribing oh my god no one equals zero
I want one we have our two lessons
this isn't right either because you
could completely exclude one of the
lists
a median of sorted arrays some kind of
binary search
oh yeah my head even close to right
outside it's just a way of thinking it's
not real coding
we might need more tea okay okay this
isn't this isn't this isn't that easy
now whatever guys oh I hate to do it for
all these people although they might not
give me a job at Google whatever I do
you know how to do it binary search to
find the slice with double and you know
map them that sounds about right
[Music]
hi OVS okay
this is hard and uninteresting way I
mean I kind of agree but I mean yeah you
want you want to implement it
[Music]
should we have races um nobody's right I
mean we can exclude anything it's not
easy it is deceptive
it is it is deceptive um we could
exclude anything from either side of the
arrays that doesn't if it doesn't
overlap 320 metric spaces
the problem is I know you can google
this one really easily
unlike the derangements one so you guys
are gonna post the answers in the wait
you taught me I can do it in linear time
all right all right go go go uh if I can
do it in linear time and pass a lot of
time out sounds to it linear time
nomes equals zero times
problems I asked him who who interviews
me I'm very hard
linear time let's kill what
we can write this offline right don't
don't pretend answer
yeah well how am I even writing this
fall
Aion short-circuit evaluation
this isn't right either I think yeah
even this isn't like super trivial -
right right because this is actually
right because if you deal with the other
edge case where this is finished
oh this is like boilerplate
okay is it really gonna start throttling
me hard
I'll put 3.5 it's not right
lists mergers right
off by one frustrating
I just solved it
you bad one time I beat out 31 percent
of people it's pretty good I think
no it's not too much at all look it was
accepted yeah nice short solution oh
that's actually a hard huh I would
actually say that's a hard decode and I
would say that I solved it that's right
should we try to write the right thing
do we even care
so this isn't a real solution guys I
mean I don't know why this was accepted
it shouldn't have been the overall time
complexity should be this and this does
not this this merge here is o of M plus
M actually can you even write the
extremely stupid one
even right the one that's so dumb you
can just do this
look at that
alright alright alright
yeah I'm not let's read the past worship
oh she doesn't look that I don't know I
just wanna look at how much bullshit
wasn't I'm not really reading it
this looks like a lot of edge cases
I employ z3
look at that check mark that's a check
mark that I don't deserve guys and that
tells you that to get ahead in the world
just you know what don't follow the
rules if the rules tell you that you
have to write algorithms that are hard
just right easy algorithms will just
tell people the door please white arm oh
oh yeah
iOS 13 will begin installing six seconds
I say what a day
all right we're gonna do two some but
we're gonna do it in a hard programming
language we did a hard one
we did one that was hard okay what do we
want
they don't have Haskell I'm sorry
they don't have racket I'm sorry PHP
what is it for dollar sign I equals zero
dollar sign I less than link gnomes this
right
for loop PHP you know might computer
lags and streaming to you guys
No Oh for semicolons because PHP
Oh call to undefined a function lack of
length PHP Wayne all right count.php
stupid oh oh I wrote the N squared
solution are they're gonna ban me maybe
they were oh that's right that's right
they say remove those PHP oh yeah you're
right I should've done the triple equals
got to make sure they're the same time
knowing guys they don't have basic this
is all they have
no more song suggestions we're not doing
any songs yeah oh that good at
algorithms not bad at all but the Cold
War's do the Sudoku one this is a cool
one think of what that is you think I'm
not much bullshit I'm gonna have to
write for that
it's like one line in Python is that I
don't think so
nothing it's a do you
if I do what
to check if a
is this hard
oh I like this it has bin support
wait this is hard this is exactly what I
wrote last time
[Music]
lower the queue the harder deaths are
you trolling me I mean this isn't
trivial right like you have to there are
there are so two to be an impossible
decision points they gonna make me log
in no they're not gonna make me log oh I
like this one it doesn't make me log in
and create this stupid account but they
try to sell me you could be an engineer
at cruise automation this is medium
what's the algorithm here yeah is there
a smarter way than just like greedy and
backtracking
how do I get the Strix how I read I
don't know how to maybe it doesn't fly
do I like have part one like this
missing language Python this is broken
ah here we go
okay um in the same order
it's just this isn't hard right it's
just if s sub 0 equals equal part 1 sub
0 ok we have to actually check if both
are true and s sub 0 equals equals part
2 sub 0 the water turn is merge S sub 1
:
right is it not oh this stupid edge case
again we need a termination to return
true yeah yeah
this is lagging and hard
[Music]
we have to memorize this - oh god well
that was a stupid type out
see I didn't even know I had to handle
extra characters
what is an extra what is an extra
character
be very careful can be formed from two
other strings
what
ah so basically I mean this is just
vicious specify this better alright and
now well see not really what you want to
do here is you want to memorize there I
solved your ass ology thing that was
easy was that supposed to be hard
Oh submitting your front line is now I'm
gonna make me sign up for an account
oh you must sign up before you can view
solutions off that's when they get you
type racer just like typing no no no
all right what else we got what else we
got going to folding laundry stream I've
been folding laundry stream permutation
free strings is this one hard the other
one was easy and I didn't like it
3q
permutation free this just seems
annoying
now I went through this one give me
something good three something fun come
on come on comment give me something
good something fun although this is like
see that's a problem you guys nerd
stange like I see this now I'm gonna
have to think about it and then I'm
gonna start coding what's this - brain
fog transpiler
this is too long to read yeah the hotter
prize yeah you're funny what Google
Chrome bounties what's this oh yeah I
don't care
guys neither that's extremely insecure
son all right we're gonna go is my iOS
13 Hall press home to finish setting up
iOS 13 hmm a few more steps and you're
done
okay appearance dark yeah bro I wish I
had an OLED all right now put my Apple
watch on oh you and Internet erasing
well that's funny bro you should feel
good about yourself everyone should feel
good about themselves unless through the
people who work at H&R Block Bobby you
were an evil person and you should be
like shit avail yourself but I don't
know most people I think they're good
how I done but otherwise most people
probably good to this number memory test
novels
I'm pairing my Apple watch but oh my
Apple watch is paired restore from
backup set up his new Apple watch I had
an old Apple watch but we're gonna set
this one up as new because it's new I'm
not trying to hack iOS guys that's
hacking like that it's like over okay do
I get beat no i don't i'm nothing good
I'm not doing typing now right all right
what about curing cancer yeah well we'll
do that next - why is hacking like that
over because it's not like there's -
good as like practice problems with the
the golden era of hacking is behind us
nobody is garbage who said any one of
those garbage nobodies garbage except
for the H&R Block died and who else no
loss in the world is truly evil
tinder sucks guys any of that shit you
know if you want to convince yourself to
never use tinder again go on tinder and
create a girl account in a couple days I
think in like a day you're gonna get
over a thousand swipes you're gonna go
over a thousand people who you could
message with and like hmm then you
create your guide send your accountant
and see them any see any matches you get
well but but that's just what it is
right what tinder functions as and and
one of the problems with online dating
apps in general is the men are on there
to get laid and the women are on there
to boost their self-esteem so these
these two markets are not quite
compatible so what you end up with is is
a ton of a ton of men who you know
validate these women and then the women
get the validation and you know
sometimes people get laid but not after
they put in a lot of effort because
that's not what most women are looking
for so there's a few things that can be
done on both the male side and the
female side of effort of dating it's I
think about this a lot um first off men
outnumber women massively on these apps
they will not tell you this but it's
true uh so what you have to do what do
you have when you don't have a match
marketplace you want to charge men money
what you want to do is say you have a
thousand women on your dating app how
many men you want to have maybe 800 so
do a do a do a second price auction and
auction off those 800 spots to the man
and you can set your bid and then once
you know your bids accepted you're
welcome to the app all right so this
gets around the there's way too many
damn men well then also these men the
men
willing to pay or probably of a slightly
higher caliber so there are there are
women who go on dating out it's not just
for validation but because they are
trying to find a date but what they get
is thousands of guys who are gonna you
know give them validation and post
one-off one-off pickup lines because
that is what most women on tinder are
looking for not for people to talk about
to talk about serious date um so you can
also you can also from the male side you
can limit you can send up to five
messages do you do away with swiping
leave swiping for the Wicker for the
women swiping might make sense but for
the men it absolutely does not the the
right strategy on these apps is just to
swipe right as many times as you
possibly can without triggering there
too many swipe right detectors tinder
reason even get a good data I really
don't understand what they're doing if
someone with a little bit of game
theoretic understanding came to the
dating app world we could live in a
world with our own eyes dating apps
[Music]
exactly right every everybody knows that
no one wants to go to a club that's a
sausage fest so you know you're a guy
you want to get into the club it's 200
bucks you're a girl you bring you know
five beautiful woman's of Instagram and
it's like six girls trying to get into
the club you know what will even comp
you a bottle of Belvedere and give you a
table right because you add value to the
club six Bros and somewhat wrinkled
shirts I mean sorry Bros 200 dollars a
piece not sharing my watch analytics
with Apple
create a four-digit passcode on your
Apple watch I say keep your Apple watch
up today okay Oh Apple pay on my Apple
watch I don't have that credit card
anymore well that's so convenient I can
Apple pay for my Apple watch oh never
mind I have to enter in my credit card
thingies my CVB's we'll deal with that
later
emergency SLS sure clock faces install
available apps all apps Apple watch I
can you know an iPhone 11 it's like the
other ones
adding more cameras does not innovation
I see video that's funny so you study in
California or go to the EU it's a very
it's a very personal decision I don't
know you how could you expect to
personalized advice you know what I'm
thinking about doing I can't click you
know I'm thinking about doing private
sessions you know think that this is
what can girls do also I'm gonna be a
twitchcon next weekend since I am a
twitch streamer um boom my Apple watch
well I don't really wanted to have like
messages and stuff I mostly just wanted
for the fitness stuff oh it like shows
me a tutorial all set I know that's kind
of nice no no I'm saying that we can
have private sessions okay we're talking
about keyboards that's born as Samar she
did some medicine work today
private sessions yeah create money with
private sessions I think maybe what's my
strategy for reaching 1 million on
Instagram I was kidding
I mean it would have been nice if it
happened but not if it's gonna require a
content strategy that's too much now
that's the question
it's one of those things where like
we're not doing exploits no honestly my
aunt is kind of good enough
I did try pretty hard for a blue
checkmark but it's really pissed when
you meet girls these days it's not like
what's your phone number it's like
what's your Instagram yo hey what's your
insta yo what's your snapchat I was kind
of joking readout of though who cares
cannot you stream on pornhub over X
videos
what do I think about cryptos in
generals bro buy some big connector bro
how's my big Connect investment doing
bid connect let's say it's going for
market cap I'm sure I'm making a lot of
money they told me that this asset
couldn't even go down I could only it
could only go up because only it could
only yeah yeah yeah why it's inactive
where'd my big Connect go Oh No maybe
Kryptos all a scam
my big connect I invested my life
savings into that i mortgaged both my
houses and sold my cousin's kidney to
buy Pitt connect oh yeah big boy gets a
real Bitcoin man really Satoshi's vision
oh that's another Bitcoin yet no shit
the stock markets a scam guys I don't
know if you've realized this but money
is a scam like the money all the money
all the money circulating the United
States do you guys know about fiat
currency like if you told this idea to
someone 100 years ago like in the future
money's gonna be backed by nothing the
government's just gonna print it and all
the populace will be so stupid that
they'll just trust it they look at you
like you are a lunatic and asked you
like you know what happened to the first
and second amendment and then like no it
turns out that people actually are this
stupid golden based on nothing yeah
currency give it some like name now that
said that doesn't excuse you if you're
if you're a Ron Paul or who screams that
we have to go back to the the gold
standard because I don't really know
about that we should think about it a
little bit more but mmm fiat money
doesn't have use value and has value
only because a government maintains its
value people is just stupid like these
people in life we wanna like accumulate
money bro
you're earning government points
becoming more real
that's the twitch bit I mean it's just
about as good to be fair the US
government does have the US military and
twitch does not but don't buying video
videos a shit stock they had it they had
a market lead you thought they were
gonna keep going with it and then the
money guys took over you know how can we
exploit all the value yeah by black
notice man you got Black Lotus from
alpha yo this can be worth some shit boy
yo guys we want guys you know you get it
the we work ICO just 47 billion dollars
it trades for 24 X revenue plus one
Apple like they make things man App
Store was it was packed last night you
know I mean if the best thing the world
is doing is like look phones used to
have two cameras now they got three you
know what the worst part is the worst
part of the three cameras is gonna be
all the Android phones next year that F
three cameras that's that's just they
don't even know why not like Qualcomm
it's very important to feature that
Qualcomm support three cameras on their
upcoming CPUs because Apple has three
cameras
Oh Android phones already out for cams
how about why my watch is ready and
press the digital card this isn't very
nice look at this you guys can't see
start the word start is cut off forget
that an apple that's upsetting oh it's a
scroll he never mind
oh it vibrated whoo that was pleasant
yeah I got a watch case
heard of GRP say we're doing a Q&A right
now what do you all want to know I've
used this before what did I use this for
yeah my pocket I've been arrested yeah
terrible crimes just Google George Hotz
arrested you could you know what I was
arrested for what's my words per minute
I hunt impact when I type I have a
minute book and a razor snorting no
thank you for subscribing
she's a mother scream Libre I wish I was
a respite at the Martin shkreli Pro des
been arrested yeah I want a possession
marijuana Megan the kids crazy
minnerath thank you for subscribing now
is the perfect time if you've been
watching my channel and enjoying my
content now is the perfect time for you
to smash that subscribe button and pay
me money alright cuz I love money and I
can buy great things like Apple watches
I don't really like this it like it's
black and then it turns white when I
look at it and then like if I turn it
back real fast it's still white I don't
know free Mars shkreli that's so I feel
you know
advice for a college student you're like
the guy who wanted advice about where he
shouldn't move I don't know man I just
know don't move to San Francisco a
pleasant shuttle SJ kzr xxx thank you
for subscribing searching for life thank
you for subscribing I love seeing you
guys all subscribe that's why we do this
here today on this channel oh you're
doing debates around politics and social
issues last something I really want to
get my voice heard on you know yeah yeah
I really want to want to throw my hat
into that arena trans Jack 7 low Quarian
thank you for subscribing thank you I'm
really really glad that you all
subscribe to my channel who you voting
for next year boom let me tell you about
the votes man now but if there's one
thing I have to say about politics is
it's really all not that important
because it doesn't matter you're gonna
vote for the you're gonna vote for the
you know it's the best thing we could do
to the government is give it less money
and pay less attention to it
politics is basically do you watch too
much reality TV right like like whenever
people ask you oh who you vote before in
2020 right like I'm gonna go up to ask
them and be like what's that new show
that was just on oh it's like The
Bachelor where they brought back all the
old bachelors it's like The Bachelor you
know reunion edition or whatever it was
enough people really hyped about that
and then like you get into real deep
conversations about like who their
favorite character is I'm like The
Bachelor forever or something right it's
the same shit except everybody in
society seems to understand that the
bachelor forever is just a TV show but
they don't seem to understand that about
politics where it's also just the TV
show
look will you ever met Joe Biden I never
met the guy man you know he's some TV
character
I am Vice President Joe Biden and I want
you to go into a booth with a curtain on
a day in November next year and you're
gonna see a bunch of names there and I
want you to make sure you press the
button next to my name because Joe Biden
is the best candidate in this reality
show politics could have maybe not get
arrested
oh my god the two days of inconvenience
my arrest caused me caught off it could
have let's see I'm I've gotta spent my
whole life no actually I really the
people who were supporting from
marijuana legalization I like you guys
I like you guys because you know what
what I think about change this actually
happened in my lifetime
that's changed it's actually happened in
my lifetime and it's positive change I
mean I don't know like a lot of change
is just like you know who's who they
grabbing the money from who they given
the money to Sasol scam but when they're
just making weed legal everyone there so
that's that's that's a cause that's a
cause that I can utter - as we get
behind marijuana legalization
good ya know if ever if ever that's a
cause if you ever are gonna make the
terrible mistake of going to vote for
something make sure it's only for mera
fixation how do you keep yourself
positive when you say everything around
you is joke what do you mean jokes are
funny man could I not be positive it's
the people who think everything around
them is serious like my global warming
is gonna come take away my bread I don't
think so man I don't think that's you
know what are they gonna take you want
weed legal because it hinders booking by
planting trees yeah it sounds good we
love trees man what are you gonna offer
on your private session oh yeah do I
have to offer something should we do
global warming's not iced it's not fake
it's real is famous real it's real
that's right I do love nature I do
if you're ever not feeling positive take
an ice cube and eat it mmm crunchy zero
calorie snack I really wanna go
what's ten curves
wash my hands Bros don't worry okay do
we have anything else to do today Oh
guys what sector of programming we'll be
safe from the recession in 2021 I mean
let me tell you something no sector of
anything is going to be safe from the
computers everything you think you're
good at a computer is about to be better
at I've wrote the hash code already
already did that sorry the stream is
kind of misleading I did that in the
first like hour
all right you know what I I know what we
can tell
I'll show you what I was I was reading I
was reading something we can read it
together I guess it's called the ghost
in the quantum Turing machine by Scott
accent maybe you guys are like
when does the supplier to use
we're gonna read this out we're gonna
read this scientific paper Raven that
wreck thank you for subscribing
wait oh you can't see it David beer
champ thank you for subscribing so you
see it has this concept called night me
and freedom I'm gonna really know what
that is so let's google it you can take
OBS any smaller windows is not usable
the hitbox is so small yeah okay
so for those that don't know Scott
Aaronson say he studies quantum physics
at UT Austin but really he talks a lot
about computational complexity Universal
genve thank you for gifting subs to
people
and Stephanie well what economists call
nightie and unpredictability meaning
unpredictability that we lack a reliable
way even to quantify using probability
distributions see that's that's like hmm
what this means right I mean usually we
think of uncertainty right if you have
uncertain to get a coin flip
then that's effectively like
quantifiable risk or statistical noise
right here courtesy even exists
I mean so you have this idea of as a
system that to predict it would require
as much computation power as to run it
and I guess that's effectively
unpredictable especially if the system
itself is the universe
Oh again you all got to talk about stuff
that if you want my advice on something
private sessions are let's say $100 for
20 minutes does that sound good
$100 for 20 minutes if anyone would like
a private session we can chat on skype
just send me an email
no there 100 there 100 that's that's the
price if you want private sessions just
20 minutes $100 just send me an email
geo hot at gmail.com and will uh what
we'll discuss it's 100 dollars 20
minutes that sounds pretty good we'll
start there and I will try my best to
give you advice on whatever it is you
want $100 for 20 minutes the only caveat
is that we're here you were there to
talk about you would not here to talk
about me like any cam girl you can't
start asking me questions about like
where I live and stuff because that's
creepy and we don't want to be creepy
not do we thousand dollars for a minute
no it's no negotiation no it's it's a
hundred for 20 though if I bore you you
are welcome to hang up at any point
yeah I saw you talks about this right so
I'll be less interested in particular
methods of prediction than the best
predictions that can ever be made
consistent with both laws of physics and
the need not to destroy a system being
studied
see I like this guy because instead of
using like philosophy terms like that
are stupid about morality he uses
philosophy terms that are we're no
longer talking about ethics metaphysics
or the use of language which is a lot of
what philosophy is all right a lot of
philosophy is just Circle Jerks in these
areas where I don't think anything can
be figured out only about whether such
in such a system is or isn't physically
predictable in the relevant way - this
is exciting because we can use science
to talk about this I reject any
connection to freedom and merely
probabilistic unpredictability I'm just
more interested in learning about this
in general
it's called sumantra PDF oh no I just
cool that ethics is not ethics is stupid
ethics is the biggest circle-jerk and
and then it and everybody who invokes
ethics is just trying to get you to like
do something it's unethical to eat me
why don't you eat beyond me instead of
catching for the beyond meat company
right
that's right whatever they want to do
they justify using ethics oh it's
immoral tough it's immoral to do that
you know more like the church used to
like oh it's immoral to have sex with
that girl outside of marriage right
today we're all like men but you know
always ask the question what they're
trying to morally guilt-trip you with
today and because in the future people
couldn't feel like we met so you know
you want to think in the future always
realize that ethics and morals are
mostly a scam we need some people who
try to talk about it genuinely but you
know Oh what did I read recently social
media hasn't made us all more
narcissistic it's just given the most
narcissistic people in our society a
platform and I'm very grateful thank you
much social media
I don't know I tried to read critique of
pure reason
maybe somebody smarter than me can
explain it to me and like say that he
was really saying deep stuff but I
thought it was mostly just confusing
let's look up critique of pure reason I
can't even remember what it was about
don't dump mercury in the food you're
gonna get sued bro and you're gonna be
the mercury food guy one's gonna hate
you man
just cuz you don't have to believe in
ethics and morals doesn't mean you want
to go we're going to piss a lot of
people off it's not very smart and what
do I think of Jordan Peterson I don't
know that much about him
I read the Kindle preview of 12 rules
for life
I don't know anyone who's Charlie tell
me what I should do
I'm skeptical of looking official thank
you very much I'm on nihilistic Milan
don't be nihilistic bro now ISM it's not
a real thing let's let's let's
deconstruct nihilism let's let's put on
our best postmodern on our best
postmodernist the rejection of all
religious and moral principles no no no
no no guys guys guys guys I think you
might be misunderstanding me when I talk
about ethics and morals ethics and
morals of course they exist but they're
deeply personal what a little skeptical
of us is when other people are telling
you about ethics and morals what other
people are trying to say to you it's
immoral for you to spit off of that
balcony all right look you might not
wanna to but you don't have to invoke
morality in this but internally without
morality and religion you are a
meaningless void adrift in a great sea
of nothingness you need to believe in
yourself the doctrine of an extreme
Russian Revolutionary Party who's the
opposite of anarchist let's see what
Google says
when running all this guy DJ he had
stuff to say he said some interesting
stuff the spa's Appaloosa that's
readable Beyond Good and Evil
this stuff is readable unreadable news
guys
we're out of tea
it's convoluted sure Infinite Jest was
convoluted you know
I think he's suggesting that I'm on
drugs as a noob and topic
I wouldn't mind look if I was
legitimately on Jar Jar I will tell you
I will confess that yesterday I took an
edible and I went for a walk you want to
see how long my walk was I went for a
nice long walk it's my friend and if I
was dreaming yes yeah I've been like
guys I took edible this morning oh well
the new health app - now track my cycle
Wow
my birthday is off by one of my weights
not right health profile
date of birth
well this is wow they really changed
everything here I'm one of their streams
or just people using phones Apple watch
edible watch stats me I don't understand
just like totally got crazy so wall
health data lights client what this is
unusable can I get the old health app
back
so all data no this isn't what I want I
want to know how far I walked
so far you're taking less steps than you
usually do
yes you look that's yesterday but it's
so bad
OMG programming is so immoral because
people lose jobs and we are all human
saves a human jobs save the clock tower
save the clock tower haircut jimmy
goodbye alright guys thank you for
watching today's stream I appreciate you
having having you all with me we did
some programming we did some other
programming we did some ranting and now
I'm gonna go read by myself my beautiful
apartment in the cloud where everything
is peaceful and everyone is happy and we
did some ASMR and we unboxed an Apple
watch which I'm gonna wear around a lot
if I'm not wearing my Apple watch pros
you'd be like George why aren't you
wearing your Apple watch
Oh